{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650861597","data":{"timestamp":" 947650861597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" dc2c7524-a324-4d5f-9ab0-d33a5f214da7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650926530","data":{"timestamp":" 947650926529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" dc2c7524-a324-4d5f-9ab0-d33a5f214da7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650926693","data":{"timestamp":" 947650926693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" dc2c7524-a324-4d5f-9ab0-d33a5f214da7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650952946","data":{"timestamp":" 947650952946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" pekee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650958927","data":{"timestamp":" 947650958927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" hajui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650964970","data":{"timestamp":" 947650964969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650970135","data":{"timestamp":" 947650970135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650977210","data":{"timestamp":" 947650977210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" mengi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650983459","data":{"timestamp":" 947650983458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" wingi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650989151","data":{"timestamp":" 947650989151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947650995290","data":{"timestamp":" 947650995289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" erosi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651001989","data":{"timestamp":" 947651001989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651007639","data":{"timestamp":" 947651007639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651013349","data":{"timestamp":" 947651013349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651019529","data":{"timestamp":" 947651019529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651025011","data":{"timestamp":" 947651025011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" apiyo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651030995","data":{"timestamp":" 947651030995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" macho"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651036808","data":{"timestamp":" 947651036807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651042066","data":{"timestamp":" 947651042066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kofia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651048059","data":{"timestamp":" 947651048058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651053276","data":{"timestamp":" 947651053276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" kutoa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651059566","data":{"timestamp":" 947651059566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" jogoo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651065627","data":{"timestamp":" 947651065627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651071551","data":{"timestamp":" 947651071551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651077339","data":{"timestamp":" 947651077338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651091577","data":{"timestamp":" 947651091576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651108144","data":{"timestamp":" 947651108144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651125126","data":{"timestamp":" 947651125126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651143861","data":{"timestamp":" 947651143861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 1c8995a7-1ffd-4a94-853e-8df9772d487a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651166173","data":{"timestamp":" 947651166173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" kutoa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651171888","data":{"timestamp":" 947651171887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651177525","data":{"timestamp":" 947651177525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651182967","data":{"timestamp":" 947651182966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651188127","data":{"timestamp":" 947651188127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651193773","data":{"timestamp":" 947651193773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" mpaka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651202391","data":{"timestamp":" 947651202391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651207305","data":{"timestamp":" 947651207305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651212584","data":{"timestamp":" 947651212584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" pekee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651221440","data":{"timestamp":" 947651221440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" hajui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651227939","data":{"timestamp":" 947651227939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651232980","data":{"timestamp":" 947651232980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" mengi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651241384","data":{"timestamp":" 947651241384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" wingi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651249083","data":{"timestamp":" 947651249083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651254108","data":{"timestamp":" 947651254107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kofia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651263840","data":{"timestamp":" 947651263840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 07f564c8-b477-4ba4-b017-01d241e423bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651280833","data":{"timestamp":" 947651280833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651299597","data":{"timestamp":" 947651299597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651316657","data":{"timestamp":" 947651316656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" mengi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651323232","data":{"timestamp":" 947651323232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" wingi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651329027","data":{"timestamp":" 947651329026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651340883","data":{"timestamp":" 947651340883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651347566","data":{"timestamp":" 947651347566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" hajui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651353380","data":{"timestamp":" 947651353380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" pekee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651359574","data":{"timestamp":" 947651359574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651365736","data":{"timestamp":" 947651365736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" mpaka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651371395","data":{"timestamp":" 947651371395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" jogoo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651377208","data":{"timestamp":" 947651377208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651382202","data":{"timestamp":" 947651382202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" kutoa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651387140","data":{"timestamp":" 947651387140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651398269","data":{"timestamp":" 947651398269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651403477","data":{"timestamp":" 947651403477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kofia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651411498","data":{"timestamp":" 947651411498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651476004","data":{"timestamp":" 947651476004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" kizee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651481767","data":{"timestamp":" 947651481766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651487522","data":{"timestamp":" 947651487521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" b99ed916-2b6f-4dee-acbe-0a9202b552cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651504734","data":{"timestamp":" 947651504734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kofia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651515446","data":{"timestamp":" 947651515446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" nyigu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651521583","data":{"timestamp":" 947651521583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651525877","data":{"timestamp":" 947651525877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" fimbo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651531533","data":{"timestamp":" 947651531533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" asali"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651537069","data":{"timestamp":" 947651537069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" fimbo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651544488","data":{"timestamp":" 947651544488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651550266","data":{"timestamp":" 947651550266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" ikiwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651556446","data":{"timestamp":" 947651556446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651561244","data":{"timestamp":" 947651561244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651573212","data":{"timestamp":" 947651573211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651578915","data":{"timestamp":" 947651578915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651586058","data":{"timestamp":" 947651586057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651595169","data":{"timestamp":" 947651595168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" jogoo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651601808","data":{"timestamp":" 947651601808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651609216","data":{"timestamp":" 947651609216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" apiyo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651615090","data":{"timestamp":" 947651615089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651619870","data":{"timestamp":" 947651619870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651625010","data":{"timestamp":" 947651625010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651629756","data":{"timestamp":" 947651629756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651635560","data":{"timestamp":" 947651635559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651649245","data":{"timestamp":" 947651649245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.init.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651661595","data":{"timestamp":" 947651661595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.2.fin.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651692153","data":{"timestamp":" 947651692153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651709910","data":{"timestamp":" 947651709910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000112_072015"," gameId":" 19762b63-832c-4318-b003-45d7946b4895"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}